<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Zambia Job Alerts</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Zambia Job Alerts</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">contact@zambiajobalerts.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">About Us</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Services</string>
    <string name="menu_aiServices">AI Services</string>
    <string name="menu_rewards">Rewards</string>
    <string name="menu_jobs">Jobs</string>
    <string name="menu_post_job">Post a Job</string>
    <string name="menu_saved_jobs">Saved Jobs</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="enter_email">Enter Email</string>
    <string name="describe_your_career_profile">Describe your Career Profile</string>
    <string name="book_coaching_session">Book Coaching Session</string>
    <string name="enter_phone_number">Enter Phone number</string>
    <string name="upload_cv_file_pdf_doc_docx">Upload CV File (PDF/DOC/DOCX)</string>
    <string name="write_requested_changes_here">Write requested changes here</string>
    <string name="submit_for_review">Submit for Review</string>
    <string name="search_jobs">Search jobs...</string>
    <string name="enter_education_background">Enter Education Background</string>
    <string name="enter_work_experience">Enter Work Experience</string>
    <string name="enter_skills">Enter Skills</string>
    <string name="work_experience">Work Experience</string>
    <string name="enter_additional_information">Enter Additional Information</string>
    <string name="additional_notes">Additional notes</string>
    <string name="skills">Skills</string>
    <string name="job_categories_it_finance_etc">Job Categories (IT, Finance, etc.)</string>
    <string name="activate_alerts">Activate Alerts</string>
    <string name="about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="featured_jobs">Featured Jobs</string>
    <string name="no_jobs_available_at_the_moment">No jobs available at the moment.</string>
    <string name="view_all_jobs">View All Jobs</string>
    <string name="submit_priority_application">Submit Priority Application</string>
    <string name="jobs_viewed_0">Jobs Viewed: 0</string>
    <string name="ads_watched_0">Ads Watched: 0</string>
    <string name="current_rewards">🔥 Current Rewards:</string>
    <string name="watch_ad_to_earn_reward">🎥 Watch Ad to Earn Reward</string>
    <string name="redeem_points">Redeem Points</string>
    <string name="our_services">Our Services</string>
    <string name="job_image">Job image</string>
    <string name="watch_ads">Watch ads to earn rewards! Each ad watched gives you 1 credit. Use credits to unlock job alerts, CV services, and career coaching.</string>
    <string name="get_job">Get job alerts delivered to your email! We\'ll send you matching job opportunities based on your preferences and skills. Note : that the subscription is valid for 2 days so ensure that every 2 days you subscribe</string>
    <string name="receive_sms">Receive SMS job alerts on your phone! Never miss an opportunity with instant notifications for new job postings.</string>
    <string name="professional_cv">Professional CV review and optimization! Our experts will analyze your CV and suggest improvements to make it stand out to employers.</string>
    <string name="get_a_professional">Get a professional CV written from scratch! Our experts will create a customized, ATS-friendly CV tailored to your career goals.</string>
    <string name="one_on_one">One-on-one career coaching session! Get personalized advice on job search strategies, interview skills, and career development from experienced coaches.</string>
    <string name="get_your">Get your applications seen first! Priority applications move to the top of employer review lists, increasing your chances of getting hired.</string>
    <string name="apply_now">Apply Now</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="load_more_jobs">Load More Jobs</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="no_jobs_found">No jobs found. Please try refreshing.</string>
    <string name="count_watched_0">Count watched</string>
    <string name="advertisement">Advertisement</string>
    <string name="job_title">Job Title</string>
    <string name="company_name">Company Name</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>
    <string name="job_description">Job Description</string>
    <string name="post_job">Post Job</string>
    <string name="channel_name">Job Alerts Notifications</string>
    <string name="channel_description">Notifications for new job alerts and saved job reminders.</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="menu_terms">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_part1">Welcome to Zambia Job Alerts. If you continue to browse and use this app, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Zambia Job Alerts’ relationship with you in relation to this app. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our app.\n\n1. Information on This App\nThe content of the pages of this app is for general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.\nNeither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness, or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this app for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors, and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.\nYour use of any information or materials on this app is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services, or information available through this app meet your specific requirements.\n\n2. Links\nThis app may include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s). Using links to gain access to such sites is entirely at your own risk.\n\n3. Content Rights\nThis app contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance, and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.\nAll trademarks reproduced in this app, which are not the property of or licensed to the operator, are acknowledged on the app.\nUnauthorized use of this app may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offense.\n\n4. Copyright Notice\nThis app and its content are copyright of Zambia Job Alerts – © Zambia Job Alerts 2024. All rights reserved. Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited.\nYou may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.</string>
    <string name="terms_part2">5. Website Disclaimer\nThe information contained in this app is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by Zambia Job Alerts and our users, and we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability, or availability with respect to the app or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the app for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.\nIn no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this app.\nThrough this app, you may be able to link to other websites which are not under the control of Zambia Job Alerts. We have no control over the nature, content, and availability of those sites.\nEvery effort is made to keep the app up and running smoothly. However, Zambia Job Alerts takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the app being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.\n\n6. Law &amp; Jurisdiction\nRecruiters, job seekers, and all other users will comply with all applicable employment, data, and equality laws.\nUse of this app and any dispute arising out of such use of the app is subject to the laws of Zambia.\n\n7. Job Seekers\nYou acknowledge that our jobs board operates as a venue only and does not generally introduce or supply job seekers to recruiters or recruiters to job seekers.\nWe accept no responsibility or liability for the content of advertisements placed on our app and expect candidates to carry out such verification procedures as are customary and prudent in the circumstances.\nIf you provide information on this app, then you are solely responsible for the information submitted. You are responsible for ensuring that all information supplied by you is true and accurate and that it is not discriminatory, obscene, offensive, defamatory, or otherwise illegal.\nFollowing registration, you will be required to sign in by submitting a username and password. You are solely responsible for the security and proper use of your password, which should be kept confidential at all times.\nWe may terminate your registration and/or deny you access to your account without any explanation or notification.\n\n8. Employers &amp; Recruiters\nEmployers and recruiters acknowledge that our jobs board operates as a venue only and does not generally introduce or supply job seekers to recruiters or recruiters to job seekers.\nWe do not guarantee any response to advertisements or that responses will be from individuals suitable for the job advertised.\nAll and any subsequent dealings between the employer/recruiter and any job seeker in connection with the job seeker’s response to a job posting are the responsibility of the employer/recruiter, and Zambia Job Alerts accepts no liability whatsoever therewith.\nEmployers and recruiters agree to deal fairly and professionally with individuals who may respond to an advertisement you have posted.\nAdvertisements that discriminate on grounds of sex, race, or disability are illegal. If we believe an advertisement may be discriminatory, we may at our discretion amend or remove the advertisement from our app without liability.\nSearching or browsing our database of registered job seekers can only be used for recruitment purposes. Using this service for marketing or direct selling to candidates is prohibited.\n\n9. Forum &amp; Communication\nAny posting of information in these forums is the opinion of the person posting only and in no way reflects the opinions or attitudes of Zambia Job Alerts.\nWe encourage debate and the sharing of information between users. However, your use of our forums and communication systems must be lawful.\nWe reserve the right to remove any content that violates our terms, including offensive or misleading information.\nFor any concerns or questions, please contact us at support@zambiajobalerts.com.</string>
</resources>